If I make a place that's a symbol, it's
kind of like the pyramids. You know, if
you look at the pyramids, the
[__] are there and they beg to
be studied because they're so weird.
Energy comes from the earth. Food comes
from the earth. Everything comes from
the earth. And I want to make a place
where everybody can see that. It's not a
theory. It is. But you've been
distracted by all this [__] that
they call you as reality. Your job is
[__] Your [__] grocery store is
[__] The things on your feet that
you keep from your real shoes from
growing, they're [__] People are
watching this like I'm a show. Like this
is a social media production. This is my
[__] life that I'm bearing for all of
you to see through great effort. So you
might see something that lets you wake
the [__] up.
>> How do I start, kid? About three and a
half years ago, I I left. I My wife
divorced me. I left just just said [__]
society. I'd done everything they told
me to. You know, I got out of prison on
8 n 10 with $50 of clothes on my back
and the love and support of my family
and just started working. Starting
working and looking for freedom. I
didn't want to work for other people. I
wanted to work for myself. Um that
wasn't enough. I had to own my own
house. That wasn't enough. I had to get
out in the country. That wasn't enough.
Then I left. I got in a van when
everybody had rejected me. Um and and I
left again. It wasn't right. I went
around just kind of like a journeyman,
equipping myself with knowledge in
various places. I ran ultramarathons,
won ultramarathons. I learned solar. I
lived off grid. I became undetectable.
Nobody knew where I laid my head at
night cuz I lived in a van. But I did
not feel safe in America anymore, man. I
can read the writing on the wall. I
don't care if anybody else notices that
I do. That place is [__] from the top
down. There's cameras on every street
corner. There's federal troops in 13
states literally snatching people off
the street, women and children, and
taking them I don't know where. It's
literally 1940s Germany playing out in
front of us. And I initially was coming
here just to do the homestead. But about
2 weeks before I was left, no, I knew it
was time to go. I feel like something
bad is going to happen on planet Earth
that is far out of our control, far
bigger than us, and is going to affect
us grievously. And even though I'm a man
of many talents and many skills, I am
far lacking in what I need to survive in
the real world. I can make money. I can
build a house if you give me lumber from
the store. Well, I can I can eat all day
if you give me food from the store. I
don't know how to exist apart from
society. And I realize that. And in
Costa Rica, I found people who do. They
get wood from the trees. They grow all
their food right here. And they live
very simply. In fact, the Costa Ricans
live 16 years longer on average than
Americans. I haven't seen a single
chemtrail here. There are no cameras in
the streets. None. Every corner of my
hometown is ate up with cameras. And I
don't know why. Why are they recording
us there? Here, nobody cares what you
do. They have a bunch of laws, but
nobody really shows up to enforce them
unless you're acting grievously. There's
a lot of respect for nature. There's a
huge family connection. There's not a
lot of screens. It's not a lot of
technology and this place just fits my
vibe. It's the first place that ever
felt like home and I had been looking
for home for a long time. Costa Rica
wasn't even on my radar. I had never
thought of coming here. Uh I was
planning to go to Uruguay to find a
remote colony living out by a sea lion
population 4 hours from anybody. That's
where I planned to go. One day I was in
a terrible mood. Bunch of [__] had
happened and I saw a flight deal for
Costa Rica ongoing and I just booked two
tickets. I sent Alex a text said, "I got
these tickets. You can come if you want.
If not, I'll cancel yours." And of
course, she went. Uh 4 months later, I
bought a house here. Really strange cuz
I travel all over the world. And came
here and just hit the buy button. And
listen,
not a man-made sound around. Toucans,
birds, a dog maybe. Man, I'm here in the
real world where I feel like I need to
be. And I'm about to bust my ass to
learn skills like pulling water out of
the river and actually feeding myself,
which used to be the only requirement
for life. But now you got to have an
address, a phone, a driver's license, a
birth certificate just to exist. And I
don't agree with any of that. Um, and so
I wanted to come here. It's also taken a
toll on me. I'm not the same happy
golucky Joe I was when I was a kid. I
used to be a barefooted country boy
without a care in the world. Just
running around catching snakes, fishing
in the woods, looking at the stars. And
just from interaction with not the
world, with humans and society, I've
been hurt and jaded and turned into,
you know, a grown man full of scars
internally that have driven me to go
further and further and further away
from what I see is [__] up and evil.
All that [__] out there made by man. I
I don't know. I don't know why I started
on social media, but 3 years later, look
at it. I I don't know why I picked up a
solar panel for my van, but 3 years
later, look at it. I don't know why I'm
in Costa Rica, but I promise you, 3
years later, look at it. And uh this is
really the first thing I've ever done
for myself. It has cost me everything
that I knew in my previous life and
loved. And this is heartbreaking to be
in a place this beautiful and just be
ate up the thoughts of yesterday and the
things that people have done to me. And
that's what drives me crazy. I can
accomplish anything I want. I can run 50
miles in the mountains. I can build a
house by myself with no help. But
overcoming the internal struggles of
just my past, that happened to me. And I
didn't do it. It happened to me. The
timing and sequence almost feels divine.
My whole life feels divine in a sense
that God never does anything nice to
you. You know, he told Noah it was going
to rain at a time when it had never
rained on earth. Never before. And it
took Noah 40 years to build a boat in
the desert. And everybody called him
crazy. You think he wasn't made fun of
building his boat in the desert when it
never rained? People made fun of him for
years. One day he got the last two
animals in there and shut the door and
it started to rain.
And Noah wasn't so [__] crazy after
all, was he?
No, he wasn't. He knew what he was
supposed to be focused on at a time when
nobody else did and nobody would listen
to him. And I feel like I'm just another
one of them. One of those people who
gets sense sent urges from above and
thoughts from below when they have to
determine the difference between them
and make decisions that are harder than
you could imagine with thoughts that you
could never imagine.
But if I've picked correctly and work
hard, he always takes care of me and I
go places that I would never imagine.
I don't know if I'm looking forward to
it. In a real sense, it's going to be
the most interaction I've had with
outside people in my life. It's going to
be prolonged 24 hours a day right here
with them. I'm a strange dude with
strange habits and a strange lifestyle
to most normal people. But it's the only
way I can see life living. I have been
living in reality for a while by choice.
That's why I don't use air conditioning
or hot water as I stay in the woods. I
try and live in the natural world. It's
how I want to live and I'm curious to
see how other people will respond to
what I see as reality. We have Leaf,
Adam, Nate, and Mason. Leaf is a
Hawaiian who lives off-rid and has been
a carpenter his whole life. He's kind of
an antisocial guy. lives on his own. You
know, birds of a feather. You have Adam
who's been doing high-end construction
in Florida for a long time. He's an
older guy, lives in a camper by himself.
Pretty good craftsman. Not sure what
he'll do with all these unstraight edges
and rough cuts. And then you have Nate
Hop, who is just a frequency being from
what I can tell. I don't know where he
lives. I've talked to him. He's been in
three different places. He's a ball of
energy. And I can tell he's been a chief
everywhere he goes. and the old saying
of what happens when two chiefs meet.
We're going to find out. I actually
think Nate will fill a large key part of
what I need here. Then we have Mason.
Mason's the oddball. He's the wild card.
He's a 25year-old kid. 23. I don't know.
25year-old kid who lives on a native
reservation. He's an Indian. As soon as
I saw him on the call, I could tell he's
a fighter. I don't know how.
And he's just kind of a fire brand. Ton
of energy. uh could also be a bit of a
problem child. When you have these four
different mindsets blending together,
I'm interested to see what they do. It's
kind of like if you ate just corn or
just butter or just beer or just salt by
themselves, it'd be terrible. But if you
have a buttered salty piece of corn and
a cold beer, it's fantastic. Maybe the
beer be okay on its own. I've never done
anything like this before. The duality
of it is kind of strange to me because
everybody coming here thinks this is
their dream. They want to live off-rid
in a foreign country. They want to grow
their food from the ground. They want to
live without air conditioning and be in
good shape and know how to exist on
planet Earth. This is also my dream.
They're getting here at the same time I
am. I had to scrape and beg and work
like a [__] dog for 15 years to get
here. Interested to see how we take
people with other parts of the puzzle
and put them together and create what I
call reality. And I call it reality
because I've been buying wood at the
store my whole life. But it doesn't come
from the store. It comes from a tree.
I've never once cut down a tree and made
my own wood. But I'm fixing to this
week. If I make a place that's a symbol,
it's kind of like the pyramids. You
know, if you look at the pyramids, the
[__] are there and they beg to
be studied because they're so weird.
They're an anomaly. That's what I do
with ideas. Like the Jesus house. I took
a concept of Jesus and put it into every
room. the artist room, the musician
room, the warrior room, you know, an
empty bird cage cross sounded out of a
door, a light that says shut the [__]
up. Everything I know about this man, I
put in there. But just like the
pyramids, if you're a mouth breathing
dumbass, you won't pick up any of this.
It's a symbol to people who understand.
This is where it's going to come from.
If you want a piece of meat in reality,
that's fine. There's the animal. Here's
a knife. go kill it and butcher it and
then cook it and you can eat it because
that's reality. But energy comes from
the earth. Food comes from the earth.
Everything comes from the earth. And I
want to make a place where everybody can
see that. It's not a theory. It is. But
you've been distracted by all this
[__] that they call you as reality.
Your job is [__] Your [__]
grocery store is [__] Your clothes,
the things on your feet that you keep
from your real shoes from growing,
they're [__] And nobody knows that
because they like comfort. People are
watching this like I'm a show, like this
is a social media production. This is my
[__] life that I'm bearing for all of
you to see through great effort. So, you
might see something that lets you wake
the [__] up. This is just me. I'm a 5'4
tattooed redneck convict from Georgia
who just said no to all the [__] they
were telling me. No matter how many
friends fall off, how much my family
rejects me, my wife won't let me see my
kids, it don't [__] matter. I am
trying to send a message and I want you
to understand what I'm doing. I'm not
making videos to entertain you. I'm
making videos to educate you. Yes,
there's hidden truth in everyone. If you
pay attention, you'll see it. You don't
need the government to keep you safe. In
fact, the safety is a fallacy. They're
here to control you and scare you into
control. Money is not here to help you.
It's here to trap you. It's like
nicotine. Once you start, you're stuck
forever. If you see this and you want to
do it, that's not some video. That's
your internal call going, "There's
something real there." And you've been
lied to so long by the media, you don't
even know what real is. You don't even
know what's real. There's a barefooted
hippie sitting in front of you with just
a camera. The only device I have to show
you a brief glimpse of what I know is
reality for this moment in time, which
will never happen again. It's a digital
memory. And I want you to see the
memories that have entered my head and
what has made me into the person I am
today. Cuz if you had these experiences,
you could not live like you live. You
couldn't do it. I promise you. In
prison, you were given everything you
need for life. You were given a bed. You
were given security guards to make sure
you don't die. You're given three meals
a day. You're given clothes. They wash
them for you. You have healthcare. You
have a fan. You have a bathroom, indoor
plumbing, everything needed for life.
But it's the worst place ever. Why? Cuz
there's no comfort there. You can't get
out. And you know it. If you had fast
food and strippers and cocaine and TV
all they wanted, nobody'd ever leave.
They've taken and they've filtered lot.
They they've changed the world. It's not
the world anymore. The law of the jungle
is the only planet there is on planet
Earth. That's it. They've made all these
rule books and there's only really one.
The strong and the wise survive. But
they've supplanted that by a red light
that tells you to stop. Why? Anytime you
see red, you stop. Anytime you see blue
lights, you clinch up. You've been
trained like Pavlov's dogs. A little
bell. They make a symbol and you react.
There's a badge, you straighten up.
Oh wow. I'm telling you the truth, ain't
I? I can go down this rabbit hole
forever. If you a tree falls on your
house, what's my instinct? To fix it.
What's your instinct? To go straight to
the local county office and ask for
permission to fix your house. Why?
Because they told you that was the truth
and you believed it. And I've realized
that through the strange lens of social
media, you can reach more people sitting
there staring into their phones looking
for inspiration than anywhere else.
That's where they are. That's where you
find the lost minds of the world. And I
could sail off into the sunset, living
anywhere I want in any way that I want
with the money that I've earned in my
life. But I spend my days grinding out,
working, learning new things, and making
videos of myself doing it just so I
might teach somebody something that
might change something. Cuz that's what
I feel like I'm here to do. I see things
different than you. I promise. We're
looking at the same thing, but the data
come on in his brain is different than
what you're seeing. And all I'm supposed
to do is tell you what I see reality is.
And I figure if I make a place that is
just too [__] cool to stay away from
and fill it full of what I know is
reality. When people come here and
experience reality, it'll be like
leaving the Matrix for a week.
And then you can go back to your busy
life and do whatever the [__] you want.
But once you get a taste of reality, I
think it'll be addictive.